All right now. I know business has been a bit slow lately. Yes, it's no one's fault.
Okay. I'm not naming any names here, Moxxie now.
Does anyone have any bright ideas on how we can get business drumming up again.
What about a car wash? This is Hell, Millie. No one cares about cars being clean here.
Okay. What about a billboard? We can't afford a billboard, sir. [Blitzo] Helpful, Moxxie.
Really glad you're in the room right now.
Have you guys forgotten what service we provide?
That was one of the good times. I don't need any reminding sir.
Considering you blew most of our salaries on an obnoxious tv ad last week. One that you
then additionally paid to have run for a
full three hours on a channel nobody watches.
Hey, excuse me. What's obnoxious about a super fun jingle? All right.
It's a fun distraction when an advertisement spitting bullshit.
People love musicals, sir. Exactly, Millie and we're basically doing a musical.
Are you going to crush my musical theater dreams like my dad did,
sir?
Because right now all I see is just my dad's asshole talking
to me crushing my dreams of being who I truly am inside.
Are you trying to crush his dreams, Moxxie?
I
...what? I thought I knew you. [Blitzo] I can't believe you
Moxxie after I made you employee of the month.
Okay, sir,
I'm sorry, a commercial jingle is not comparable to musical theater?
Nobody actually likes the jingles. [Mille] I liked it.
Do not do not agree with him in front of me.
Hi there. I'm Blitzo! The O is silent and I'm the founder of I. M. P.
Are you a piece of shit who got yourself sent to Hell? Are you an innocent soul?
Who got fucked over by someone else?
After lovingly killing my wife for fucking a delivery man.
You can imagine my surprise when I wound up here after the state of Ohio killed me.
I really wish I could stick it to that yappy jogger who saw me hiding the body.
Well, luckily for you, thanks to our company's special access to the living world.
We can help you take care of your unfinished
business by taking out anyone who screwed you over
when you were alive. [*jingle*] When you want somebody gone and you don't want to wait too long.
[*jingle*] Call the immediate murder professionals
[*jingle*] Hand grenade or cynanide, we'll make it look like suicide. The
[*jingle*] immediate murder professionals. We do our jobs
[*jingle*] so well, because we go straight up from Hell
[*jingle*] We'll kill your husband or your wife. We'll even let you keep the knife!
Mhm.
Doctor. He's not responding. More water, stat! It didn't do anything.
Damn it. I'm not losing another one.
Holy shit. It actually worked.
He appears to be in stable condition, but he'll need surgery.
What insurance provider do you freaks have?
The fuck is insurance?
...kids die for free!
I'd like to go on record and say that incident was Loona's fault,
dispatch is supposed to give us the right info on the target.
It's very simple. Oh, sit on a dick, Moxxie. You sit sit on a...
and then do your job. Now we don't blame our screwups on Loona. Okay.
She didn't do anything wrong? Are you kidding me sir? She's awful. I
Hello, I.M.P. (phone) What if I got stabbed?!
Happy adoption anniversary loony. I got you a little something.
Is it a cure for syphilis?
I...
Then I don't want it!
I'm sorry, my spiders. Goddammit. Excuse me. Did you just fax me an ad for weight loss?
No why why would anyone send me this? Come on.
You know why
whoever left the fucking avocado salad in the fridge?
I'm taking it because I have the worst hangover right now.
Why would you drink on a work night? I'm hungover from this morning dumb ass.
Isn't that my lunch? You know what?
I can't take this assault right now I need to blow off some fucking steam
That clingy rich asshole is on the phone says it's urgent, wants to talk to you.
Sounds a little D. T. F. Oh God it was one time
if I hadn't slept with that privileged asshole.
None of us would have access to the living world.
You what?
Got the book, Got the book.
Not this fucking heavy book. Oh shit
sorry I fucked your husband. How hard you already know what can I do you for?
This time stole us.
There's a political candidate causing trouble upon
earth for a few of my associates.
He's trying to convince people global warming exists. (Blitzo) Doesn't it?
Well yes but more people die if nothing is done about it
and it gets lonely here.
Okay, well um yeah, that makes sense.
You know what happens when I'm lonely, Blitzy. (Blitzo) God fucking dammit.
When I'm lonely, I become hungry and when I become hungry,
I want to choke on that [***]
of yours
[***]
and lick all of your
before taking out your [***]
and [***] with more teeth until you're screaming
[***] like a fucking baby
eat this.
And then you know that bridge over the freeway? Yeah, shit off it.
Look, the point is,
Loona is a valued member of our family and we don't get rid of family.
We aren't a family sir, you are the boss,
we are the employees. You treat her like she's some troubled teenager,
she's more like a meth, addicted homeless woman.
You let man the phones. That is offensive.
Without homeless people, I wouldn't have half the joy and laughter I do in this life.
Mhm.
What?
While we're on the subject of family,
can you stop finding me and Millie outside of work?
Come on, sweetie, It's not that big a deal. Excuse me? What
honey, can you give me the butter
sir, sweetie! Spoiler alert. The butter spoiled.
What's funny honey. Really impressive wordplay. What? Why are you in our fridge?
Oh
what you're dreaming about?
I was dreaming my parents were being murdered, but now I'd like to go back to that
of all the instant Hell it's for him that I am. Oh mill
yeah,
are you fucking filming us right now? Just stop doing that.
I don't see what the issue is there something you don't want me seeing?
Know your baby Weiner?
Haver, sir, what you say and how you act as totally inappropriate, calm down Mox.
You're going to have another panic attack. (Moxxie) I am calm! There, there.
Look, I don't judge the boring couple stuff you do outside work hours,
so don't judge me for what I do.
Judge you, sir. Quite a lot actually. Mox, he's our boss. No, it's fine Mills.
Your husband is just...how do I say this? Without being offensive...retarded?
Does immaturely insulting me? Make you feel better about your sad single life.
It actually does. The only reason you have a wife is because you're easy to manage.
No, he's not! You bitch! (Blitzo) Do not talk to my receptionist that way. She's sensitive.
Yes, I am. You guys are all fucking assholes.
Yeah.
Oh, shut up, kid. You're lucky to witness this.
This company is such a mess. All right, let's get back to talking about my outfit.
Nobody was talking about that. Which is why I'm trying to get that ball rolling.
So how does it look? It's good. Right.
It's been a literal Hell having to pretend to be paralyzed.
You fuck shits wouldn't kill me. But now I want that. I want death.
You are a selfish, greedy clown and I'm a kid.
We're supposed to like clowns, even the creepy ones.
Hey, now that's not very... (kid) If I wanted to hear from a spineless jackass,
I'd rip out your spine and ask you some shit.
That's my husband you're talking to! *laughs* That's your husband?!
I figured you for a slut, but I didn't know you needed dick that bad
And you. [Loona] What? What about me? Nothing. I don't talk to dogs. I'm a cat person.
Yeah,
...wow. You know, kid, you kind of are a piece of shit.
Oh fuck guys. I just got a text from our client.
I guess he was the right target after all.
Who him? Me, yep. They wanted us to kill an actual child. That's what they're saying.
Well, Christ on a stick. I guess there is a God,
You know, folks with this company,
I really wanted to prove that we're capable of doing
the same things anyone else can. Like killing people.
So from us here at the Immediate Murder Professionals Group,
we promised to settle your unfinished business or your money is gone and
you're never getting it back and you can write us a bad review,
but we'll play dumb to it because it's Hell and no one fucking cares.
You know, even though this kid was a target,
he's still a child,
It's important that we've handled this going forward respectfully.
Please. If anyone has seen my little Eddie, please contact us.
Oh,
you're welcome.
Oh, what a thrill when the crimson starts to spill and my Millie goes in for the kill,
she takes away my breath.
She's the angel of death for me. Oh Millie, she's McQueen. It's like a dream
when I hear her victims start to scream in and out of the sack. She's the maniac for me.
Oh Millie!
When the blood starts dripping down the walls and the bodies start to fall,
my heart skipped a beat
when my Millie's guns a blazing in the heat.
My assassin love, She makes the murdering fun for me. A lottery of all the incident.
Hell it's for her that I fell Omilami
mm