Uh huh.
Mm hmm.
I'm sorry for having to move our little rendezvous early.
I have an engagement this month on the full moon when this happens.
It's not really something I fuss about.
But do you really need the book for this farm bullshit?
I have like 15 new clients waiting for heads to roll.
As shocking as it may seem glitzy.
My grim wa is actually incredibly important and it isn't supposed
to be lent out to depict the intent like yourself.
The harvest moon is a very special occasion.
It's been my annual duty to showcase it in the ring of Wrath.
It's celebrated by a very charming little festival with the locals Wrath, huh?
My employees are from there. I've never really been here.
It's full of inbred chuckle. Fucks. Oh, why don't you all join me at the festival?
I can guarantee you all special excess. Look, I told you we're not bodyguards. Okay.
That was a one time thing we did badly. I'm simply offering a work free day of fun.
I feel quite safe at the harvest festival. It's the same every year.
Well, if you promise, this isn't some fuck fest invite.
It does sound like it could be a blast and a half plus.
It's not like we can do Jack shit without your book anyway. I'm sorry.
Your clients who have to wait. Oh, fuck my clients.
Really?
What do you want sir? Hey, hope I didn't wake. You mocks.
How would you and mills want to visit the
Wrath ring for some harvest bullshit this year?
The harvest moon festival. You
fuck it all. Well, Milly likes the idea.
Wait,
where are you calling from? Mm?
Of course
you can do that.
Uh huh
Oh,
daddy. Hell's my deadly little pumpkin spice. Do it. I'm good pop.
Thanks for letting us stay here for the harvest jamboree. It's no trouble.
We know you aren't making as much anymore
since y'all went freelance freelance pays fine mom.
We're doing fine. It's fine.
Anyway, y'all remember? My husband might see
readings win joe.
How have you been with all the flaming twisters and stuff around here?
We lost our old farm head to one of them payrolls last week. Oh, crumbs my bad.
I am so sorry. I didn't mean to open that wound
sir. Hey, watch it. I'm the sir here, bucko. Yeah.
Y'all haven't met my boss blitz and his hellhound. I'm not just his hellhound.
Yeah, she's my daughter. Only on paper.
Y'all don't deserve to know my name.
It's a pleasure to finally meet the sperm and egg
factory that popped out this little gem of an assassin.
You to raised a sturdy bitch
that we did. So glitches it there. That's a fine name. It reminds me of war.
Uh, nothing like a little war to make a strong man. I like you.
People, you know more battles were won by technological advances in warfare.
I've researched the history of weaponry extensively and it's inspiring.
How, for example,
the progression of guns utilizing angelic technology
has changed the landscape of hell's combative.
I mean, we're fun guns get the job done.
But a man ain't nothing if he can't hear the
head off a hellish beast with only his bare hands
is right Mugsy. You've got q widow baby hands like your baby. Didn't refrain
sir. Springing a strong hands. Y'all should meet our newest help.
Hey, strike her.
Well, howdy!
Oh, lookee! Here, you must be the famous mildred.
Heard some good things about you from your folks. Little lady.
What are y'all doing so far away from em city? A free working finally slowing down.
Oh no, freelance. He's in free. It's a
never mind.
We're just visiting for the festival. The prince is our boss's boss. Friend Millie.
I am not above hitting a female in front of her daddy boss, Huh?
Oh, So you're the bold attempt to start his own killing biz? Yeah.
Well, when you're good at something, you should probably capitalize not many.
Start businesses on their own.
That's pretty impressive sir. Oh
yeah, it is. I guess.
I guess it is, isn't it?
So you even con that ditzy blue blood into getting you to the surface.
Well, it's long and complicated, but the short answer is yes, but he's not like,
you know, we're not we're not doing it.
What's between?
It's a transactional fucking you see, you know,
you boys should enter the pain games.
I heard games. What games? I'm in every harvest festival.
There's a competition to be the roughest toughest bastard and ram. Yeah.
I wish I could play millie. You know, you get too carried away.
The last competition ended in 15 separate funerals, I'm aware.
But I only cause none of them. How come Sallie Mae still gets to compete.
Your sister doesn't have a neighborhood head care.
She so does it doesn't can if they don't find the body still,
you get to root for her and your brothers and now you can cheer on your boss.
You know, she can also cheer for me. Way you. Yeah, I could compete, can't I?
Third boy. But I don't think sensitive sp in types would last very long in the games.
I was born here too. I have some fight in me, huh?
Well in little fella,
won't you help me wrangle one of them hogs for dinner. Simple. Watch me with these
bullets can pierce the shell. You gotta get the knot underneath them.
Pry yourself an opening. Oh right, right.
I knew that. Just remember your rep with the in laws is on the line here.
So no pressure at all.
You totally will not make an ass of yourself
in front of everyone important in your life.
Go get them tiger. Oh mok. You don't need to do this.
Oh, he totally does take a class moxie. Yes.
Up.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Right in
thinking that bitch. You won't call back in the morning. This is fucking beautiful.
Doing great moxie. Send me that video later.
Mhm
Oh my clavicle. Don't worry little one, You never stood a chance. Hey boss man,
you want to help the men skin this thing for dinner?
Oh, I am always down to skin the manly. Meet with the manly man. That's what she said.
What? Who said? Wait, what bitches talking shit about me.
Don't let him get to you And hey, you don't need my parents to respect you.
They will eventually. No, they won't.
What?
I'm right, aren't I? Oh, I'm entering those games.
How pissed would you be if I bet on him dying.
Welcome all to wrap the rings,
annual harvest moon. First of all to kick things off. We have the great Prince Olav
here to usher in this here pang game, how kind Blackfoot greetings,
Tiny wrath ring imps.
I hereby welcome you all to another year of celebrating the
spoils of your labor that continue to feed the citizens of Now
I'm happy to kick off the start of these games that
will challenge the toughest imps to show their skill and dominance.
Good luck to you all.
Especially that sexy little one there you glitzy.
Fuck me.
Okay.
Hi!
Yeah,
yeah,
mother fuck!
Say for the first gear. Whenever we have a
for winner of the harvest moon paint games to win is on strike
darling.
You say my name, right, you fucking dick. All right.
So he has the physical advantage I'm better at other things like singing.
I'd like to take this opportunity to sing a quick song.
I wrote just now about me winning.
I smell the stench,
open
victory. Everything
Every
isn't this guy great
half.
It's gonna be nice working with him. Working.
What? Yeah. I asked him if he wants to join I. M. P.
You asked.
But
marks, I think you've had enough for now. Let's head back to the house and you clean
you go fuck yourself
or something.
It was just a word. Thank you. You took out.
Okay.
The whole
Uh huh.
Mm.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Well, that's troubling.
Oh, my crumbles genuine carmine crafted blessing tipped rifle. How,
how when the fuck did he get one of these? Why don't you ask me little dude shit?
Why do you have this?
Mr?
You are aware this kind of weapon can kill demon royalty.
Yes, that
no shit.
That's kind of the point.
Okay, well, I'm relatively concerned by your possession of this.
I'm also glad my instant dislike of you has been validated.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Mhm.
Good.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Oh.
Mhm,
pathetic.
Mhm.
Mellie.
I'd kill you all,
but I feel like there's more leverage with your rodeo clown of a boss.
If I don't
Plus your little things ain't worth to clean up
millie.
I'm satan moxie. I'm fine.
I got worse than this during the flower toughs in my brother's wedding.
But I call that fucking bouquet and it was fucking worth it.
You just have to get out there and fuck up that brown nosing cocksucker for me,
but I can't break through it.
I'm not strong enough. Not with your hands, baby. Use what you're good at.
I'm not good with my hands.
Oh right.
Yeah. Yeah.
I probably should have used this earlier. Uh huh. I love you honey.
But for fuck's sake, my dear communist of the Ring of Rock. I
stole us of the arms. Go Alicia
here by curse this year's harvest with the globe of the true harvest moon.
Excuse me the fuck Liz. I thought you were still at the ceremony.
You thought I wanted to stand around with a bunch of hillbillies
excited about corn and shit with a thirsty owl on stage.
Now you seem disappointed in me.
Yeah, well,
I'm not a fan of someone I offered a job
to about two off my easiest lengthy ticket to earth,
bind my back lists.
Come on.
You know, the two of us are superior than most of our kind.
And you were so above sucking on a disgusting rich pompous Croatia
only to sneak topside for scraps and work for bitter centers.
Who could care less who you are when you could be slaying overlords.
Why struggle to run a business that is rigged against you.
You could partner up with me and kill
the unkillable.
Starting with the one that treats you like a play thing. That's kind of hot.
We could be the most dangerous beans in hell.
Let's wow, that was a good fucking pitch in workshop in it.
You know what? Fuck it
I'm in.
Uh huh.
Took you long enough marks. Well you should have seen your dipshit thing. What?
Bull? Okay, cliche much.
Oh you daddy fucker.
Mhm
Yeah.
Oh
yeah
you dumb. Fucks lost the upper hand fast. Huh?
You seem to have forgotten something. Fuck Oh.
Mhm.
A fucking dammit luna. It's a damn shame blitz.
We might actually have made a good team.
Not well. And your wet dreams, you hockey talk.
Mhm
I still think it's embarrassing.
You're wasting a lot of potential, relying on a week list.
You're gonna finish that fucking sentence.
Hardener vermin
who's weak now. Big, okay, I'm here.
Maybe you'll get me next time.
Let's see.
Mhm
Mhm.
I can't believe you let him trap you really haven't. We talked you better.
I was seeing Red Ma and he was slavery excuses. You're better than that mildred.
You know she protected
and maybe I'm not a strong beefy dickhead.
But Millie has the strength enough for both of us.
You two are getting on her case about being hurt by a psychopath. You hired
shame on you. Oh moxie, look at you speech and like a big boy with his big pants,
wow! He noted. He's never acknowledged your input before. So is that progress
uh failed to kill the target at the festival.
But don't worry, ma'am,
it won't happen again. It's better not. I want this cheating prick dead.
I don't care who you have to go through. Make it happen,
understood.
I'll get him next time.
Sweet.
Everything. I
every talent type so much more talented than you, every time I try
push it and succeed me.