Mhm.
I love this song
hair.
Holy shit.
How you suck for life. Do you listen up? You want to know pink conduct you?
God.
Oh shit
Rosica,
let's so I should have known you'd be here, I can smell fish for miles,
which is odd because I believe the nearest ocean is three rings down and
I should have known you'd be here when I heard the amber alerts.
Oh yeah, I'm surprised to get your fat ass out of rehab.
I can see you're still a drunken whore clutching onto that Bielsa juice bottle.
Like it's the last cock in hell.
They let me out because I'm still famous and rehab is for sad loser wash ups.
So your sister says, hi, why are you parking here?
This is the only parking spot my company has.
So take your tampon race car somewhere else actually, Prick,
it has my name on it.
I'm doing a bit of freelance for one of
the infinitely more successful companies in the building.
No,
they would have you come in this week to lead their team during spring break a week?
No, no, you are not parking here for a fucking week, You matt.
Let's so you're gonna run off leaving someone else to pay for the hotel room,
Steal their car and run three racetrack and
max my credit cards on shitty horse lessons.
Goddammit whore. You will not let that go choke on a sandpaper cock.
Yeah,
hold on, You better move that pussy wagon right now or I'm gonna,
you would, or I'll call Hr
anyway, me and my new hellhound Vortex.
Unlike you, He actually does his job well, to, to fuck stain.
I wasted so much time with a bag of holes like that. You know? Veronica made a
Oh yeah, I heard, Yeah, we dated. Was it before or after? She became a pop star.
You dated a pop star? Okay. Why are you all acting like That's such a shock. Hello.
It's veronica Mayday. It's you. I just she blind
suffering some form of brain damage.
Okay, look, you are all making this into a way bigger deal than it needs to be.
I don't pry into your stupid personal lives. You do that. Do that, sir.
Well, the sex with her. Like do we what? It's a pop star.
You want to know what sex with Michael. Crawford was like,
touche. Okay, look, let's just drop it.
Really find a temporary spot for that truck. Okay, Looney moxie.
Let's go handle this shit. Do you think they saw me?
Fuck, I did my makeup shitty today. You look perfect Loony like always. Shut up tech.
Oh, let's
why?
Uh huh.
Oh
wow.
A big man with your bitch bag of an employer. She's in her office.
There wasn't room on the second floor. So they rented one here on this one
cheapest. Oh, come on.
Sorry man. Oh no, you don't bitch. How about you?
Let me go in and try to reason with her.
I don't really listen to what's classified as pop genre music.
So girls status to me is
riveted.
Shut the fuck up. All righty then.
Yeah.
Hello Miss Farrah sica. Was it?
I work for imp and it is actually rather important for us to retain
the singular parking space we were assigned because look at the little one.
He's got a widow Botha. Please don't condescend me, ma'am.
I want to kiss your little guy a kind offer, but
I'm married. Hey, why don't you send a little message from me back to your limp dick
boss.
You got
Mopti Don't let her access any of your home.
I gotta go lie down now.
Oh, this won't stand.
All right.
That's it.
If you're going to be shitty to my employees,
then I challenge you to a fucking challenge.
Fuck, I said that twice.
Mm. Is this in boy starting a demon duel? I think he is.
What's the game then blitz?
So every year you STD spreaders go up top side for easy pickings
while Spring break is a prime time for crime of all kinds.
So I bet you suck.
You bitches can't fuck as many people as we can off by the end of the day.
Oh, you're serious.
Game on bitch.
All right. Shut your assholes. Here's how we're gonna do this shit.
First we find a fuck ton appliance. We portal up. We have our fun murder time.
As per usual. We pile all the bodies into a big fucking canoe.
We push said canoe into some water.
We light it on fire to attract the sharks and ego shit. Maybe a goose to fuck it.
They come and eat the bodies.
We win the bet, we rub it in that sloppy bitches, drunken whore ass face.
Do you have any question? Uh yeah, Why was that nonsense? That wasn't a question.
That wasn't a plan.
I'm sorry, but that was a flawless presentation of what we should do,
mox It's not my fault.
You got a smooth little brain upstairs right now. I'm calling you slow moxie.
God, why don't you learn to take criticism? You talentless baby dick troll.
Well why don't you take an art class? Why don't you see how expensive they are?
Hey, is there a way I can come with you guys this time. Absolutely not.
I forbid it not gonna happen. Sorry, sweetie.
Spring break is no place for young, vulnerable. Got girls.
You know, the kind of freaks up there who drool all over you?
Well, I can blend in with humans easy enough. Just let me tag along.
Wait, say that again. I can blend in. Do you have a human discuss? Yeah, don't you?
Yeah,
you three have been screwing around on earth
this whole fucking time without human disguises.
Okay, new plan
Looney can help lure the humans to us and we'll take care of the rest.
Okay, how about that? Wallace logic.
I think you're missing the biggest issue sir,
isn't it crucial to have a client who demands enough kills to win this bet
we are just going up to massacre. I got that covered mocks.
Now we wait, sir.
There is no way we are going to get enough clients by
the end of the day with one poorly spelled bad grammar flyer.
Now, who's first?
Okay,
remember we can't be seen. Alright. And loose shots will likely cause a panic.
So luna can help with leading targets to a better spot to offer them. You got the list.
Loony
got it.
Hello honey, look at you. You look downright awful. I am so proud now bitch.
Mhm
understand you.
Yeah,
mm
Yeah.
Mhm
mm
mhm
Yeah,
that's nine kills in the bag. I'd like to see that whaley snatch orgasm. That many
free breakers. Y'all ready to get fucked up and make some bitches bitch.
What?
This is your final boarding call.
All aboard.
Thanks
signs
because
okay babe,
can start to move
down.
Goddamn it. That bitch started her goldfish mating call now.
She's gonna win all these sex maniacs. We gotta pick things up guys
on the list. Loony, Huh? Yeah, I think so.
God.
Whoa, whoa. What are you? Leper con? Yeah, pretty cool. Huh.
But you sure as shit. Ain't gonna tell nobody. All right. Next one.
Come on buddy.
What? Where's my baby?
Does it smell?
You're nice.
No.
Yeah.
Hey,
you Hey, you're the hound. Working for my boss is freaky ex. Yeah, sorry.
If that's weird, it's cool. Her beef a mine.
I'm not paid enough to care. Yeah. Yeah,
I'm luna.
Okay. Hey. Birth head,
that's hot.
I mean like literally, you know, because vortexes, you know, they give off heat.
Probably right. Yeah,
I guess.
But my friends call me tex.
Oh yeah, I wish I had friends. I mean, I don't have friends.
Am I interrupting something? No man.
Just having a conversation, conversation leads to HPV and we've lost him.
It's looking like it's up to us to handle this list. Hell yeah.
Team in the name of getting shit done making the money.
Let's get the fuck out of here. You're gonna get us all into shit.
I just wanted to see what was so important that you'd be distracted from your job.
What? I can't have a break. We have a parking spot on the line.
Hey dude, won't you chill out? Why don't you stay out of it? Okay, this is our business
literally Fuck Blitz.
Why can't you stay out of my face for like five
minutes because I adopted you and that should mean something.
What does it matter? You're not my real dad. I was almost 18. It still counts.
Well, it shouldn't. I didn't need you then asshole. I don't now. Mhm.
Yeah.
Found.
Oh my God. It's a fucking pathum crime. I got it should.
Okay.
You're faster.
Yeah.
Uhh let's I'm enjoy your break loony. I'm gonna go kill something? Damn girl.
That was savage.
You ok? Yeah, I'm fine.
He'll get over it. He always does. I'm glad you can stick up for yourself at least
takes guts. Thanks.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Potsie,
Millie. Hi.
Hey, Hey, where did you get for heads?
I want to kiss him.
What?
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Mhm.
Ooh.
Yes.
Okay,
mm
And
and and
Mhm.
Yeah.
For
Mhm.
Yeah,
I love that woman.
She totally pegs you, doesn't she?
Yeah.
Oh yeah. Way to show off. Mills.
Is mom okay?
Oh yeah, I'm fine.
This is funny
and so
drinking.
Okay, this is too wholesome for my liking blitz so. Oh perfect.
That must be the whores that was handled rather
obvious. Don't you think? I don't think this belonged to any of us
would be a shame if anyone found out you guys
were behind a giant monster fish in the human world.
Oh, satan, get out himself.
Yeah. Well you three nasty ass gremlins will be in shit for not being in disguises.
A human called me a possum.
I am not a bottom.
You know, we could keep this little B movie sane on the down low.
If you agree to let us use that parking space.
Fine. We fucking what?
Yeah. And your face bitch.
Come on,
let's get out of here
Tax.
Well
guess it sounded bounce,
but hey,
if you ever done the party,
I'll give you a ring sometimes. Really?
I mean, Yeah,
yeah,
yeah. My girlfriend throws a ton of crazy hound parties. Nice.
Can't wait for my first one. Let's get you some friends girl. Come on looney tune E.
Let's go back and park are fat fucking car in our fat fucking space,
wow.
Uh huh.
Right,
Yeah,
I remember,
wow.
Mhm.
Put your hands up you sick deviant.
All right, let's get ready to suck a lot of pig dick.
Mhm.
Me on finding out
saying you want cross cross the state effects even showed it to
a file made you were a bit kind of general leave.
Well, I'm a wet wild stallion and out running free
steps out my nut. You tore me apart. Just left up my moody and you tangle my part,
but there
and your shatters my heart, buddy.
What is love?
Yeah.
Oh my
switch your puberty twice.
Mhm.