mommy. Yeah.
Yeah,
livia is calling a Stella. Here you get up.
Fear. What troubles you? My our let
daddy,
Daddy.
I had a dream. A really bad dream.
A nightmare. I was looking all over the palace
and I couldn't find you anywhere.
He was there
there there via It's okay. You're okay
when you're scared
and you don't know where I am. You must remember.
No matter what happens to me,
I will never be far away from my special little starfire.
It always seems more quiet in the dark. It always feels so star.
How silence grows under the moon, constellations gone so soon.
I used to think that I was bowled. I used to think love would be fun.
Now my stories have been told
except for one
as the stars start to
I hope you take it as a sign.
Okay. Everything will be OK.
And ever seven rains go lattes. Although the day could be my last. You will be okay
when I'm gone. Be okay.
And when creation goes to
you can find in the sky upon the lost. You will be
you slept with
a fucking bath. It wasn't expected. I didn't have time to go to the hotel
like a fucking plebian.
The world is burning down around here.
Yeah.
You want to fuck this one to know. Of course. Ask You are a goddamn embarrassment.
I'm not spending another moment looking at your pathetic imp sucking face.
Mhm
Well, john
mm
Good morning. Octavia did you sleep well, my old let a serious question.
Mm. What's that? You're listening to?
This song is called My world is burning down around me.
It's by fuck you dad.
It's a band. Oh,
how charming
You two done screaming for the day.
Yeah.
You know what? I haven't done in a long, long time.
I haven't taken you to your favorite place in all of hell. Why don't we go to lulu land?
I'm not five anymore. You always were so happy when I took you to lulu land.
What do you say? We go there again? Have a day. Just the two of us.
I'd rather kill myself. There we go.
Anything but staying in this house now I'll arrange our security.
Security for a theme park. We're rich and we're hot.
People want our money and our bodies. Money. Maybe speak for yourself princess.
I'm calling the only man who can what?
Who can protect me us being part of the go Isha family is rather valuable, you know?
Oh blitz. You're such a good path. Yeah, I really want you sir. Me too.
Let's three way way.
What? Why? Hello. My big, dead glitzy.
What the fuck dad Language? Everyone, I have a special request.
Look, I just had a chemical peel.
So you'll have to find someone else's face to plant that feathered ass.
It's for my daughter. We'll make sure she washes it. No, no, no, no, no.
I'm taking my daughter to lulu land and I
was hoping you Brave little ims would accompany us.
Where assassins? Not bodyguards. Okay.
Don't invite us to shit Unless someone's gonna die? I'll pay you.
Pay me what money done
coming? I'm getting here. We're going to little little that lulu
lulu land land.
Mhm.
This stuff.
Mm
mhm.
Now remember this is work and work.
Only me and my crew are not here to satisfy your perverted bird means All right,
right.
That
do we have to
hold on right there, sweetie.
If you try fucking my little ass in that park, I swear to you.
So cute when you are serious. I'm literally going to be sick crumbs.
I knew today would be a lot. What do you need? And
I'll be broke into morphine. That was figurative old man. Oh right.
But she said it was literally
what?
I haven't been to this place since I was a,
it hasn't changed a bit.
Oh, it's a big move lee that is deeply upsetting. Oh, come on. It's fun.
You've never been here.
No
theme parks always disturbed me.
Especially the mascots. Well, hey there, I'm lulu. Welcome to lulu land.
If you all get hurt here, just try and sue us. Look here, it's lulu. I have a question.
We'll ask away. Little girly
isn't true.
This park is just a really shameless spinoff
of Lucifer's far more popular lulu world.
No, this place reeks of insecure corporate shame.
Why don't we go check out the rides? That shakes creepy.
Wait till her dad tries to diddle your holes. What's that mean? Don't talk to me.
I know you're a pervert under there.
Yeah.
You really like this place. Huh? I love this place.
My parents would bring me and my siblings here when they could swing it
money wise. Yeah. The prices do seem rather crimen.
I mean that much for a novelty cup that you use one time because it's lulu land.
Listen to your home marks
habit. I take the first watch while you to have a little fun. We gotta do my favorite.
Right?
Oh yeah. Which one?
Yeah.
No grounds.
Yes.
Mhm.
You know it's quite thrilling to see you on the job. Let's say that bitch.
I'm working.
You both need to get a room. Hey I am not a day hooker.
What I just said. I'm not one brood.
Oh look feel you used to cry such tears of joy at this show.
I hate that fucking clown
ability. I need my bodyguard.
Mhm
Oh.
Mhm.
In place it's the the robotic viscerally shipped from the
factory to bring you a wonderful show celebrating
lulu land spell with those two ongoing lawsuit.
A
hello Hello. Step right up and win a thing. Oh look maxie.
Oh you like that thing. Yes.
I don't really know what that thing is but I want that thing.
Finally some
thing I can handle.
Okay
one game please.
Yeah.
Oh strength. One little man but I hit it. I don't know what to tell you bunny.
The target. See
it didn't go down.
So yeah, no go bro.
Yeah.
Mm
The heavens wrong with this thing? Oh man. A real shame. I tell you what
Uh huh
Oh
another, I sing along with the little blue band. Every boy.
Every girl, Every woman, every man with
Oh how delightful.
Oh my What could aim you have? Let's see, I can't do this anymore.
We just
Octavia.
Oh, is that lit? So my sensor spot a bear.
I guess the kidneys are still running away from you.
Not always silent now.
Just like your audience always was when you told your lazy jokes here,
bitch, I make more money killing people than you do.
Being a cheap ass robo rip off of an overrated sellout jester. Someone salty.
Really not. The people love me. Does anybody love you?
No, but I'm really good with guns now. Dance bitch.
My country.
Yeah.
Fight me torches.
Get your inconvenient torches here.
No.
Yeah,
wow man, you're really starting to make this sound.
You know, if you suck, you suck. Guess you won't win your honey here. A crane.
Let me track.
Yeah,
yeah.
Oh look at that lucky shot baby. Are you kidding me?
You charlotte didn't, Hey, I get lost pip squeak. I'm talking to the lady
mhm
now
sir. Hey guys, you should probably go make sure stole us is okay.
I've got some unfinished business to take care of?
Yeah.
Oh, what a mouth?
Many people
God Joey knife in. You ruined another body photo. Why were you even born Octavia?
Leave me alone. Octavia.
Um, I think I'm supposed to be body guarded right now.
God, that's better. But where is glitzy? He's my knight in shining armor.
Not you littler ones. He's up.
Big thing being a fool. What kind of fool? Everything is now on fire. Kind.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Octavia.
I take it you of
not having fun.
I didn't even want to come here. I'm sorry sweetie. I
thought you loved it here.
Mhm
And I was a kid and my parents didn't hate each other.
My dad didn't feel it was a weird red decade the entire time.
I'm sorry via I'm sorry for
everything happening right now. I know it's a lot. I I should have listened.
I just want to go home
but home doesn't even feel like home anymore.
You ruined it.
You need to understand
your mother and I
I just
I felt
mhm.
She has always been
I haven't been that
we weren't in.
I'm sorry. I don't have the words.
Are you going to run off with him?
Believe me behind.
Go away Where?
I can't find you. What?
No,
no, no, never. I'd never do that.
Never.
I think it's time to leave this place. You were right. You are too old for it anyway.
So what would you like to do now can we go to stylish of coals?
They sell weird taxidermy there. Mm. Okay,
likes dad.
You're a guy sometimes. Thank you via. Thank you.
Way to ruin another good things. Way. It. That slutty toy, clown hat it coming way.