Mhm
Right there. This was the first sighted, they are definitely from hell.
They must use this dark magic to cross over into our world
and they seem to be killing specifically targeted people?
But why they always attack at random all over the country?
There's no way to predict where they'll show up next.
Oh well that's convenience.
Remember we can't be seen part of my words, sir,
but you're currently being the loudest.
I said, shut your dick sucking lips, moxie.
Yeah,
luna hold it
calories
back off you tuxedo wearing bucks.
I'd like to see the suits and corporate calling us losers. Now,
that was pretty bad ass.
Super bad ass.
Mhm.
Shit. Shit. Shit shit. Uh You okay there? What are you doing? Sitting there?
The boys are in trouble opening the can blitz was
using a total of zero euphemisms innuendos or swears.
That means it was serious.
Which means I don't open it until open the fucking part now.
Oh
yeah,
they aren't here.
Mhm.
It smells like they went this way. Come on, Let's find the dumb ass twins.
Mm hmm.
Uh huh.
Finally awake, huh? Little fella, Your papa has been for a while now look shit bag.
It takes a lot to keep me down. All right.
I took a fuck ton of tranquilizers in the college I dropped
out of Also I've been strapped nipple first to a car battery.
So okay. Tell a steaming scum.
Who do you work for? Satan? How did you get to our world from the afterlife.
Why use killing humans. When did you show up here?
Okay, I'm gonna stop you right there bitch.
First of all,
we just woke up from a very nasty shock and I'm still feeling fucking woozy.
So I'm gonna request that. Just some coffee before we get into this.
I mean everyone gets coffee and shitty movies with scenes like this. All right.
I want something iced bitch marks. I'll have a Neopolitan cappuccino.
More cappuccino. Make sure it's got no more than four ounces of milk.
The beans won't have the right texture otherwise.
And make sure they spell my name correctly on the cup. They always put foxy roxy.
I hate that if you can't handle that,
I'll have a venti traditional misto Please use soy milk with two blonde shots.
I forgot him and restrict out.
I'd also love three vanilla pumps at the very bottom, then add the coffee after then.
And now we are getting his coffee, wow, I was getting massive douche chills.
Just their marks. Congrats.
If we have to We are willing to resort to torture
methods to get answers out of you nasty hail beasts.
When you say to our church, you mean physical or psychological.
Physical seems counterproductive.
We would likely tell you anything if it meant an end
to the pain and you would have no way of knowing
what was true or we might like it too much And
then you've got a whole new thing to deal with.
What do you mean by that? You're stupid, huh? I could work with stupid daddy.
Likey dummy.
You can relax,
dad! You better stop laughing at it. Yeah, you are the ones at our mercy.
It's hard to resist. I'm really sorry.
I mean, considering your approach thus far, you've had us tight here for what?
Hours? And you haven't even had us confirm what exactly we are. What are you?
I'm a Virgo. A smart guy.
More quip out of you and we'll shut you up. Getting kinky.
We aren't playing any of vile demon kinks.
I mean, that's what it sounded like back there. You're sick.
Oh, please don't give them ideas, sir. Why not? I know the shit you're into.
We are not getting kinky with you, calm down one. Don't let these monsters get to you.
Hey, are we going to get our phone call, bitch? Well, that entirely depends.
Who are you going to call your fat mom? Thanking her for a fat time. Nice try demon.
His fat mom is. Dad
is where they ended up, I think so. Fuck, this looks intense.
How are we going to get in, lift me up to that vent?
Mhm.
Yeah.
Damn.
You're pretty agile for an old lady. I'm like five years older than you.
Stop insulting my mother. She's dead. Hey?
Let's just leave them here until they feel like talking
When?
Yeah,
don't worry marks. If we keep being obnoxious.
They'll eventually slip up and we'll get a chance to get out.
Let's just keep fucking with them until they get so frustrated.
They stop thinking clearly. It usually works. Hmm.
So the demons want to play games, huh?
Well we can play games.
I'm just worried about Millie. She'll be on her way by now.
I'm sure she'll be fine, moxie.
It would take a roided up hippo to take down that woman when she's upset.
We've never dealt with the human government before. She's in danger.
Do you ever honestly shut up about Millie? It's always, Oh, how's Millie?
I can't tonight. I'm hanging with Millie.
I'm still worried about Millie and she's always five fucking feet away from you.
It's pathetic.
That was oddly personal. You're right.
I don't know why the fuck I just let my guts spill like that.
Sir.
They're filling this room with something. Fuck hell is this?
I think it's some kind of airborne truth telling Sarah.
Oh, you just guess that's what it is. Well, just ask me something specific.
I wouldn't normally tell you. Okay,
this. Milly ever pegged you sometimes. Wait you. Fuck, why that I knew it.
Your suit is tacky. Fuck. I'm sorry.
How fucking dare you. You have shitty taste in music. I'm sorry. Shit. Taste.
You said you liked that musical. I recommended to you. I lied.
I left halfway through. You said you loved it. It was awful moxie.
It was about ugly, horny cat.
I think I've said so many lives.
This is gonna be a good night.
Oh
damn it moxie? This is all your fault? How is this my fault?
Mhm.
Yeah,
blitz. I can't see you. God, this smells awful. What's that music? Is that you?
Is this a prank? Because I swear this. It is no prank bitch. Hey,
why do you sound like that? Because you my precious little bitch boy.
Stop it, tripping balls. Know what? How could this be?
I've never tried to ask the truth or D. M. T. It's a bad trip.
Like a vault. Of course blitz. This would be your fault.
My lungs are full of honesty. Would you promise me that you won't judge?
Not trying to divulge too much, but I'm in too deep. So first of all, fuck you.
This is just typical.
Well two can play at this game of
despair because if you're here causing frustration,
I'm torturing you in your hallucination.
Mm.
Yeah.
I simply follow your orders. It is it my fault?
If your orders are as non sensible as a son panning
left out on the
porch of refreshing?
Why are you talking like that? What the fuck does that even mean?
I am simply speaking state of plain english?
Perhaps don't crack open a dictionary sometime
and then maybe you can understand
top of the privileged thing by getting all and an all
around on my system and the last one on top.
Yeah.
Shut up.
Why do you hurt me? I know why
I push my friends.
Why does it seem like a recurring thing that you alienate with your toxic routine.
Don't know. Eventually everyone is your thoughtless and ruin.
You'll end up alone every my
You don't know what you are doing half the time.
And you depend on me and the missus to manage your foolish flights of fancy.
You can do this
on my own.
Yes.
What
you're trying to
get you still shove away anyone who gets too close
until they resent me for being a selfish shit.
Are you afraid?
I've
found consciousness trying to tell you that
you simply cannot fathom proper intimacy,
but also craving as well.
It's rather unfortunate sir,
considering it's often how you treat those who stand by you such as myself.
Are you worried? I may have enough of it one day as well.
Stop fucking talking all of you.
Why maxie? Why have you held your true feelings inside? A rejection?
Must see why do you have merely put it in your book? Gives me an erection
a to why we accept your true feelings. So promise me that I can do to be true.
The world is your brain is so pegan with honesty. I've been a jackass.
It's true in a Jackass. It's true as we're back as ourselves. I will be a better friend
then I was before.
Be better at speaking my mom
together. We can begin to become
fine
try one.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Do you remember what you said to me after my first day with the company?
Not really.
I remember
he told me I did a good job and
that you were proud to work with me.
I feel like you wanted to say something more judgmental. But
he said that because I needed it
and it helped look, I'm hard on you because I know what you're capable of mox
you care too much about what everyone thinks except
for me because you know my opinion is correct,
but just keep doing a good job.
Okay, You shoot and kill good. You escape things easy.
You could be strategic and cold blooded when you
need to and don't expect any more compliments.
I'm maxed out. Thank you sir. You know my name,
use it. Thanks blitz.
There's my millie impressive work males. How'd you get here all by yourself,
looney. Get your asses out here before. More fuckers show up.
Yeah.
Oh.
Mhm.
Okay. I've had one. Too many emotions for today guys. Let's fuck me fuckers off.
Cover me.
What? I'm just so damn proud of you loony.
Hi.
Hey males,
just watch
you need a gun or anything.
How about some water?
Mhm.
Split.
No problem in nearly Billy.
You want some quality time with daddy.
We only use the weapons from Japan's Edo period.
The period was better and you know it
correct.
Thanks.
Hey ma.
Oh wow. Really? Going for the dick there, aren't you here? I got it for you.
Oh hold down.
Oh yeah. Getting hard. Hold this motherfucker!
So crumbs.
Is everyone okay? How's that for demons? Some
Mhm
Oh shit. Come on. Families below this toxic joint.
Okay.
Great book.
Shit. I can't
I can't read the spell in this light. I can't see dick.
Well shit, looks like we've built this weapon tip dry and now we're out of badasses.
You demons aren't going anywhere now.
Mhm.
Mhm
Who dare threaten
my english
lady.
Mhm
distraction.
Ancient auto.
Yeah.
What's the matter? Demon hunter? Never seen a real demon before.
Mhm.
This is
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh
huh.
Mhm
stolen. Well, hold on. How did you know that? We needed help? I have my ways darling.
Are you all right? I'm fine stole us. Good. How the fuck did you get caught by humans?
Are you little creatures not being careful up here.
You know if you get in trouble, I get in trouble, be don't want that.
They caught us off Guard your highness.
Yeah. You can unclench your bird postal. It's not gonna happen again.
Okay, luckily for you Most don't believe the word of the demon obsessed lunatics.
They are seen as kooks
kooks.
Such a silly word.
Now let us all return? Yes, please.
I'd like to get back to the correct hellhole as soon as possible.
Am I going to get any.
Thank you for the rescue bitsy now I suppose you
should want me to fuck your brains out tonight.
Very much so. All right, But you're keeping quiet or I'm using those bear trap.
Oh, please do. Well, I'm around,
Yeah.
Mhm.
So what now? What now? We finally got the evidence we needed to be taken seriously?
Nobody in corporate is ignoring this.
Mhm.
This was a mistake. It was a horrible mistake.