Mhm
Howdy! I'm cleanest! Welcome to heaven.
If you did something good to get here and
good people deserve to give loved ones special blessings.
Does it make you want to cry
when your face is turning blue, luckily for you, there's something we can do.
We can help keep them alive.
Are you beat now? We never even scott B
and we're here for all of us.
Nice one, baby.
Give me another mock
now. I'm not feeling it. Next.
Uh huh keep going, keep going, keep going. I see, I see. Are you looking to get work?
Making crazy contraptions and goofy gadgets?
Well,
call me and wacky wally white birds like the idea of factory
where you make the things and I make the money please.
I'm very desperate bingo
on the road
guys,
do you feel that? Oh shit, is that a hail shake? That's possible. All right,
don't panic, moxie, I'm not panicking because how quakes don't happen.
Stop getting hysterical fatty.
Who do not be afraid. Please tell me you got that insurance thing. How are you?
And what do you want to have you
dusted the inventor of all things Loopy and
got to just use the door. Dude
doesn't need to be this whole thing.
I am eccentric and must therefore too eccentric shit.
Oh, this old fuck reeks of the living world. Did you just die this moments ago.
In fact, Which is what brought me? Yeah, just saying
the front door would have gotten you here. Shut up dear furry!
This is the man I'm gonna need you to kill?
Not even a ship's length of time in hell and already plotting revenge.
I gotta respect a man with that sort of passion. I'm blitz the O is silent. What?
Oh no, thank you. Now what's the tcs fatigue guys help? Why are we killing this guy?
I mean, what did he do to you see, he was my business partner. You see,
I was not always an old man.
My partner, Lyle and I ran lyle. You be robotics. A technological empire.
Earlier today we were testing a new machine
intended to stop or reverse the aging process.
That could have seen the whole three trillion.
There's unfortunately we neglected to test the machine
on the poor like we usually do.
We were too sure of our own genius,
but the machine was accidentally set forward by the time we managed to get out
it was too late.
At least for me.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Now that evil son of a bitch is going to take over the empire we built together
without me to share it with.
You make all the goddamn money in the world and
become the fourth trillionaire and get all the credit.
That's not really evil. It's evil towards me.
Everything
he's going dot.
Now get your crimson asses up above and send that heartless
No good son of a bitch bell where he belongs.
You do know poopy Loopy.
Of course, of course if we do kill him though and he ends up down here.
You know, you will be stuck with him forever. Trust me. Yes,
I'm counting on it. That's gonna hot.
Yeah,
gee, I wonder whose house this is Until you're right.
Is the home of famous inventor, lyle Lipton. Ooh, let's do it gang.
Let's kill this rich guy.
And here you'll find three tacky stalkers about to attempt a murder.
Things like this could happen to famous people all the time.
Yeah,
wow, That machine really did a number on him. Goodbye. My one true love.
All the riches of the world can't fill the emptiness.
I'm feeling now that my shitty old body can't do anything of value.
How fantastic he's gonna do our job for us.
Uh
Should we go in there and tie it for him?
Yeah.
Mhm.
No, Lord. I'm being haunted by ugly often Children now. Who the fuck are they?
Oh no, sir. Those are Karen's Mr lyle. I hate filthy stinking often.
Children were here to convince you not to kill yourself sir.
To grant you a blessing on behalf of those in heaven
benefited by your amazing
technological advances. Oh, hell no!
Don't receive.
Fly a Lipton. It is our
humble opinion that you should continue the process to commit die.
I mean, what do you expect to do with all this money now? You're old and gross.
Is that a serious question?
He could help spread his wealth around with the people of the
world and do so much good with it and be so fulfilled.
No, he could pay for new hospitals and schools. Why won't you let me die?
I'll sounds like you need help often yourself there buddy, moxie.
What have we got for this fella?
I have some assault weapons, crossbow, hunting, bow, Tommy gun,
old fashioned shotgun, revolvers and three colours.
James, scott, honesty's classier than that.
There are still plenty of reasons to live. Mr lyle.
Yeah right smells like he ain't been out of bed in months.
Let's can be beautiful at any age and we'll show him. Yeah, look around last.
God's gift of nature is a wonder to behold regardless of age or well
if you were to end your life you'd be missing all of this.
You're gonna buy that load of shit from a baby and the sheep. It fucks.
That is so inappropriate. Kiss our ass! Prude! Anyway, take it from me.
A fellow genius. Nature is no picnic up close.
Oh
stop,
I can't stop. I
want to die more than I do.
Let's check out some places.
Oh Lord! Where are we? Now? Let me perish. We're here to show you another thing.
Life is worth. Living for childhood of wonderment. Why
look at those sweet, disease ridden vermin.
Their joy comes from innocence unspoiled by the burdens of a dog hood
and their middle class existence. Such simple joy they have.
It is inspiring.
Thank you for showing me this. Hey dipshit.
I want to see whose lap you're sitting on?
Uh huh.
Mhm
Oh,
this place reeks of teenagers.
Lover's lookout, sir.
We're here to remind you about possibly life's greatest enjoyable money. No
love. I've never been in love before,
I imagine it's quite nice. It's not too late, sir. You can still find fat.
Nice, try ugly. Hey, horny lovers. Which one of you would fuck this old man.
Mhm.
You know, you three are so utterly cruel.
We're just trying to give hope to someone in need.
Oh and you three are so superior to us.
Just because we want some selfish, greedy,
authoritarian capitalist to keel over dead.
You're making things too real Now, moxie
behold the wonder of art and music, something always there to comfort,
entertain and live for.
So how do we make this bad? We can't There's literally nothing bad about opera.
That's fact. Unless we ruin it somehow.
He's not very good.
Yeah.
Oh at least we made it bad that I had it.
You three monsters have messed with us and us too. We're just trying to do a job.
Well, so are we?
We are saving that shitty old man's life whether he wanted or not.
Well, someone wants that fucker dead. Okay.
And he paid in advance and I spent it all on this so he's gotta go Yeah,
all such disgusting loathsome feast.
Your kind is nothing but dirt that shetty dead people dread on
And now you're trying to meddle with the lines of him?
How are you?
So why don't you shut your trap, you judgmental cotton candy tin having bitch.
Selfie.
It's all starting to make sense. Now
life is worth living because we only get one.
We must cherish it
if creatures far beyond this living world are going through these legs over my life
and suddenly it's worth living.
Killing myself is not the answer.
Plus
I'm still rich,
I could just buy all the things
I no longer crave. Gods.
Yeah.
Oh
brother.
Okay.
Yeah,
wow.
Yeah.
Well, well would you look at that? You did our job for us.
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Oh my God. Get hold of yourself. Calling.
I do not use the Lord's name in vain. This isn't over.
Mhm.
Yeah. No, sorry cletus. But I'm afraid your actions resulted in the death of a human.
I'm afraid you can't reenter heaven. Yeah, No. Yeah, I'm sorry. Yeah. No.
Is there
anything we can do? Yeah, no, no, no, no. Oh no. What? We didn't need to. We never.
It was all
anyway. Sorry guys. But those are the rules. Yeah. Way.
Well, the old man wanted to live again and we didn't kill him so we failed.
Thanks to those fucking cherubs. He's probably up in heaven now. So
it's a shame. All our client wanted was eternal revenge on his business partner.
And now the two are forever separated?
And now we got to face the fire of fucking up sir. When are you going to tell?
The client already sent him a text and we're in good hands his text.
Don't make people angry.
Mhm
Place
Lofa, we can explain everything. I was
lyle lifting. I don't understand. We thought you went to heaven heaven.
They don't make millions in technological advances and
robotics by not experimenting on the poor.
So you know, good heartless son of a bitch.
Thank you for reuniting me with my best friend.
The only question now is what do two old
genius robotic inventors do now that we're in hell?
Did someone say?
I say inventors name's Wally Waxford and I
am looking for creative new people to exploit.
I mean in pull everyone stop fucking up my walls,
moxie is gonna have to fix all this shit chill out marks,
you can kiss my ass any harder, you'll go right inside me,
satan's balls first we deal with heaven's table scraps.
Now this I guess you can say you say you have a holy operation here blitz so get out.
I said no I'm serious, get the fuck out
mhm
mm
Uh huh