I was a good person before it all went down I was good my entire life.
Mm
Good morning.
I hope you all did your homework,
we did your homework and you have our teachers and then when I
threw out these fun questions you should notice what to do to plus 60
and good behavior and it's now that part of the class when we
say the time of day and date nine in the morning on january 8th
and it's your husband's birthday
and that
mhm.
Yeah.
Oh my stars
stop singing Children hush up now,
I forgot it's my husband's birthday. I didn't get him anything special.
If we call him we could do a happy birthday surprise. Okay yeah,
we're not your things right there. Oh yeah,
okay. Not there, not there, not there.
Okay wait this is me buried. Remember what you taught us. Think before you act.
Mhm
Okay. Oh shit, sweetie! What are you doing here? Shut up carol!
You scream like a thick
Oh God, what have you done? She had a family. We could have had his family.
Oh dear God. What have I done
in front of you all?
I'm so sorry my Children don't forget to work on your time stable.
You do everything right in life.
Played by all the rules and still get sent down here with all
the Hitler's at Epstein's of the world after one measly massacre propelled by.
Blind rage. So that's why I'm here
to get my revenge. I mean was she hotter?
I'm just saying I had a hard time understanding the unprompted melodrama,
you just spat at me tits anyway,
I don't think you quite understand how we're operating down here.
See we take revenge out on the living and it sounds like the core cast of
your sitcom of a death frankly are all probably down here in hell with you.
Not all of them That horse survived now. They all call her a hero.
How does it feel to have survived such a crazy bitch.
I just hope that sick woman finally found pace. You are so brave. Here's $2 million.
Oh thank you
between the talk shows and donation bullshit. She made so much goddamn cash.
Getting shot was the best thing to happen to her. You're a hero. You're a hero girl.
My mom was a hero. She is a hero. Your hero. Your
hero. Your Oh
okay.
Oh you're a hero. She's not a oh yeah, okay. Yeah. My thoughts exactly
moxie stop shaking. You're gonna shoot are only hail ham, wow. I feel so loved here.
Just take a deep breath and let it out.
But it's a family under what circumstances would we ever need to kill a human family?
I mean if that's what the client wants, maybe like a shitty dad or a mob family
that's understandable but to eradicate an entire innocent,
seemingly in this instance.
Upper middle class family bloodline. Hey you don't know they're innocent.
This kid probably sets dogs on fire.
Maybe this girl gets off to bullying Australian kids online. And this guy.
This guy definitely watches Exactly. Humans are full of secret nasties.
It's why so many of them end up here.
But guilty and innocent aren't our business mocks.
Killing who were paid to is our business shoot the target.
I just think it's a bit excessive and we could be a bit more selective. Is all dance.
I want you to meet
our newest client.
It's
damn it, moxie, I just cross those heels.
Bye.
And don't worry, we'll get that skank in less than 24 hours or your first kill is free.
When did we start implementing that deal?
When you set fire to my office in front of a quiet, you fucking Dick Shit.
Now someone please tell me that fancy book is still intact.
You mean our only ticket to the other side? Yeah, got it.
And that's why you're my favorite Looney. You get a tweet now, stop, you're so gross.
Oh, stop it. I got enough of that from my therapist. Now let's go lick some ass.
The expression is kick some ass blitz. Mine's better.
Fuck!
Yeah,
that's gotta be her. Oh, this is too easy
moxie. Do you want this one? Me?
Yeah.
This one simple enough for you to handle just a
happy mother who just got out of the hospital.
You snooze, You lose marks and I got you bitch.
Wait, are we actually killing a family. No, don't be a puss.
We're just killing a mother were ruining a family. But
hold on, hold on. Let's just think about. What was that ralphie? I don't know Martha.
But whatever it is,
they're gonna be tomorrow night's dinner.
Mm.
All right, kids, guns out. Looks like he got some rabbits to catch young'uns.
What the fuck was that, moxie?
I'm sorry. They just seem so wholesome and happy. I panicked.
Who the fuck is innocent moxie from the moment of birth. You already?
A parasite leeching off your mama's kids.
Get the fuck over yourself, your baby dick. Tracy.
A new hole scatter.
Yeah.
Oh
yes,
yeah,
Yeah.
A little critter.
You can't hide long for me.
Mhm.
Okay.
Yeah.
Car.
Yeah,
it's
Oh
well. Hello. Little ones. Aren't you cute? Not have a new credit to play with you. Is
Yeah.
Oh,
crumbs.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
I know.
Little day.
I promise. I can make that pain go real quick. Just come, let me know my Marsa.
Put a bullet in your pretty little scout.
Okay.
Damn it.
This is a really bad time. When isn't it? At that time? Let's see. What is it?
I've been meaning to follow up in our
last little conversation regarding my grim watch.
What did you just call me? My book?
Let's see the book I was given to do my job that I have allowed you to use to do yours.
Can hear you darling. Shit. Any who I have been thinking.
You know, I have been permitting you to access the mortal realm less than legally.
For some time now but I do need it back to fulfill my duties. I was thinking
what if we worked out some kind of exchange favors for favors?
Doesn't that sound enticing? You gotta stop using your fancy ass rich people talk.
Okay I'm trying to concentrate on not getting fucked in my age.
Then let me keep it simple once a month on the full moon.
You return the book to me followed by a night of Pershing good for
location and you get to keep it all the rest of the time.
Sound fair. My little imp fine whatever. Oh blitz. I'm so excited.
I cannot wait to feel your slimy
inside of my
so yeah we'll tell them. Huh? Come to drag me and my kin to hell. Well
not today, satan gonna send you all back where he came from.
Mm.
Yeah.
Yeah
belly.
Mm.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah
I had that fucking shot.
Goddammit moxie satan, we return your filthy creatures back to the pits of hell.
May the root of evil remain honored as we continue my work.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah that's not exactly how it works lady.
Sorry your fire doesn't really hurt us but I mean
I could fake it if that'll get your dick hard.
Oh
shit.
Well I'll just shoot you in your smart ass mouth. That would be more effective blitz.
You're not getting your goddamn paycheck for this one box.
Yeah,
yeah.
Oh yeah, Thanks. I'm fine. I'm sorry sir.
I compromised our objective and put us in harm's way.
It won't happen again. I promise, apology accepted.
But if you ever pull a stunt like this again, I will fuck you and your wife.
Alrighty job. Well done. Now. Let's get off. Yeah, give me a moment.
I need to get something. I left at the house. Okay, fine, but hurry up luna.
We're ready to come home. Dear.
Mhm.
Use well, you and I am
jelly sandwiches on.
Don't move. What are you gonna do? Little guy kill us.
I should you people are monsters, but you should have a chance at a life and a purpose.
Look at your Children. They have their whole future ahead of them.
You are going to face your crimes Justly,
I will call your earthly authorities and they
will make sure you are dealt with fairly.
I'm handling this my way. Oh shit. Uh Do you uh you have a phone to summon 911?
Yeah, it's in the kitchen then. What is this for? It's a universal remote.
Got it for the kids. Oh,
there he is. Have a good wank off session, moxie? Excuse me.
Look, I don't care where you come in the living world. Just come to your job on time.
All right. See you at the office.
You doing okay, sweetie better now, honey.
I think I just needed a minute to process you. Have a good heart, honey.
Just a fuzzy head.
We got our boys.
Yeah.
Yeah,
yeah,
Yeah.
Okay. See my little months. Oh, yeah.
Well, here's to another mission accomplished.
And moxie finally learned not to fuck up and killing people.
Isn't that big a deal If they try to kill you back, That's messed up. But I paid for it.
Yeah. Fuck that family.
Yeah.
Well,
mm hmm.
Mm.